const questions = [
    {
        question: "Which company made the game Rust?",
        answers: ["Facepunch", "Blizzard", "EA Sport", "Rockstar Games"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "How much wood do you need to make a Tool Cupboard?",
        answers: ["500", "1000", "750", "100"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "How many metal fragments are needed for a Sheet Metal Door?",
        answers: ["125", "100", "200", "150"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the monuments is not a save zone?",
        answers: ["Outpost", "Military Tunnels", "Bandit Camp", "Large Barn"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the monuments is a save zone?",
        answers: ["Airfield", "Harbor", "Large Fishing Village", "Launch Site"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "How many locked crates are there on the ship?",
        answers: ["3", "2", "4", "1"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the fastest horse in the game?",
        answers: [
            "White Thoroughbred",
            "Black Thoroughbred",
            "Buckskin",
            "Dapple Grey",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "How many locked crates are there on a small oil rig?",
        answers: ["2", "1", "4", "3"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "How many locked crates are there on a large oil rig?",
        answers: ["0", "4", "2", "1"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "How many workbenches are there?",
        answers: ["4", "7", "3", "10"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "From which monument can you buy a boat?",
        answers: [
            "Fishing Villages",
            "Water Treatment Plant",
            " Train Yard",
            " Oxumâ€™s Gas Station",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "From which monument can you buy a Minicopter?",
        answers: ["Satellite Dish", "Outpost", "Airfield", "Bandit Camp"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "With which tools can you get wood?",
        answers: ["Hammer", "Rock", "Jackhammer", "Torch"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "With which tools can you get stone?",
        answers: [
            "Camera",
            "Handmade Fishing Rod",
            "Stone Hatchet",
            "Stone Pickaxe",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question:
            "How many metal fragments are needed for a Sheet Metal Double Door?",
        answers: ["190", "250", "200", "300"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "How much scrap is a single minicopter worth?",
        answers: ["750", "1250", "650", "850"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question:
            "How much scrap is a single Scrap Transport Helicopter worth?",
        answers: ["750", "1250", "650", "850"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question: "How many Military Crates are there on the Dome?",
        answers: ["5", "2", "3", "4"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        difficulty: "easy",
    },
    {
        question:
            "How many Heavy Scientists come to the Small Oil Rig when The Locked Crate is released?",
        answers: ["8", "9", "6", "7"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question:
            "How many Heavy Scientists come to the Large Oil Rig when The Locked Crate is released?",
        answers: ["10", "12", "14", "11"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "How many Scientist is there on the Small Oil Rig?",
        answers: ["20", "17", "16", "14"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "How many Scientist is there on the Large Oil Rig?",
        answers: ["23", "30", "26", "27"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "What size ammo can Python use?",
        answers: [
            "Explosive 5.56 Rifle Ammo",
            "12 Gauge Buckshot",
            "40mm HE Grenade",
            "Incendiary Pistol Bullet",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "What size ammo can the LR-300 Assault Rifle use?",
        answers: [
            "12 Gauge Slug",
            "Pistol Bullet",
            "5.56 Rifle Ammo",
            "Rocket",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "What ingredients do you need to make an F1 grenade?",
        answers: [
            "Gun Powder:30, Metal Fragments:25",
            "Sulfur:100, Gun Powder:50",
            "Metal Fragments:25, Gun Powder:30",
            "Gun Powder:25, Metal Fragments:30",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "What ingredients do you need to make an 8x Zoom Scope?",
        answers: [
            "High Quality Metal:30",
            "High Quality Metal:50",
            "High Quality Metal:25, Tech Trash:5 ",
            "High Quality Metal:45, Tech Trash:10",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question:
            "What ingredients do you need to make a Medical Syringe Blueprint?",
        answers: [
            "Cloth:10, Metal Fragments:10, Low Grade Fuel:10",
            "Cloth:20, Metal Fragments:20, Low Grade Fuel:20",
            "Cloth:15, Metal Fragments:10, Low Grade Fuel:10",
            "Animal Fat:30, Metal Fragments:10, Low Grade Fuel:10",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "What ingredients do you need to make a Holosight?",
        answers: [
            "High Quality Metal:12, Tech Trash:1",
            "High Quality Metal:10, Tech Trash:2",
            "High Quality Metal:1, Tech Trash:10",
            "High Quality Metal:10",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question:
            "What ingredients do you need to make a Triangle Ladder Hatch?",
        answers: [
            "Wooden Ladder:1, Metal Fragments:200, Gears:3",
            "Wooden Ladder:2, Metal Fragments:300, Gears:5",
            "Wooden Ladder:1, Metal Fragments:300, Gears:3",
            "Wooden Ladder:3, Metal Fragments:100, Gears:2",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "What ingredients do you need to make a Gears?",
        answers: [
            "Metal Fragments:50, Scrap:100",
            "Metal Fragments:100, Scrap:10",
            "Metal Fragments:10, Scrap:50",
            "Metal Fragments:25, Scrap:100",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "What ingredients do you need to make a Key Lock?",
        answers: [
            "Wood:75",
            "Wood:100",
            "Wood:50",
            "Metal Fragments:25, Wood:25",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 0,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question:
            "How much scrap will it cost you to buy a Blue Keycard from Outpost?",
        answers: ["Scrap:150", "Scrap:200", "Scrap:100", "Scrap:75"],
        correctAnswerIndex: 2,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "How much is the power consumption of the Auto Turret ?",
        answers: [
            "Consumption 5 Energy",
            "Consumption 10 Energy",
            "Consumption 12 Energy",
            "Consumption 8 Energy",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 1,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    {
        question: "How much is the power consumption of Large Neon Sign ?",
        answers: [
            "Consumption 5 Energy",
            "Consumption 3 Energy",
            "Consumption 10 Energy",
            "Consumption 8 Energy",
        ],
        correctAnswerIndex: 3,
        difficulty: "medium",
    },
    // Add more questions here
];

const filterQuestionsByDifficulty = (maxQuestions) => {
    const easyQuestions = questions.filter(
        (question) => question.difficulty === "easy"
    );
    const mediumQuestions = questions.filter(
        (question) => question.difficulty === "medium"
    );

    const selectedEasyQuestions = easyQuestions.slice(0, 5);
    const selectedMediumQuestions = mediumQuestions.slice(5, 15);

    return [...selectedEasyQuestions, ...selectedMediumQuestions];
};

export default filterQuestionsByDifficulty;
